【声音】
[SOUND].
啊！
[LAUGH]
Content Providers
Content providers.
恭喜大家，你们已经完成构建Sunshine应用。
Congratulations, everyone, you've finished building the Sunshine App.
但总有空间给更多的阳光。
But there's always room for more sunshine.
是的Dan，但是现在是时候
There is, Dan, but now it's time
让学生去构建他们最终的项目了。
for the students to go build their final project.
你们可以从Android开发者网站上
And you can get a lot of the resources you
获得构建一个超赞的应用所需的许多资源。
need to build really great mobile apps at the Android developer site.
也可以从我们和Udacity这儿获取更多。
And stay tuned for more from us and Udacity.
现在，我想是时候来些蛋糕庆祝一下了。
For now, I think it's time to celebrate with some cake.
哇欧。柠檬挞。
Woohoo. Lemon tarts.
【音乐♪】
[MUSIC]